Hyeonwoo Cho

Seoul, Korea

■ chochb123@gmail.com | 🏠 hyeonwoocho7.github.io/hwc.github.io/ | 🖸 github.com/hyeonwoocho7 | 📠 www.linkedin.com/in/hyeonwoocho/ | 📾 Hyeonwoo Cho

Bio_

Hyeonwoo Cho is an Al research engineer at OSSTEM, a healthcare artificial intelligence company based in Seoul, South Korea. He received his MS in computer vision from Kyushu University in 2022, where his research focused on domain adaptation and semi-supervised learning. His research interests include continual learning, test-time adaptation, noisy label learning, and 3D vision. He has developed a Al system for early diagnosis of lung cancer. He is currently developing a tool for analyzing multiple diseases associated with dementia from brain MRI.

Education

Kyushu University Fukuoka, Japan

MS in Information Science and Electrical Engineering

March 2020 - March 2022

- GPA: 4.0/4.0
- Lab: HumanInterface
- Advisor: Ryoma Bise
- Research fields: Computer Vision, Bio medical image analysis, pattern recognition

Kyushu University Fukuoka, Japan

BS in Aeronautics and Astronautics

March 2016 - March 2020

• GPA: 3.4/4.0

Work Experience _____

VUNO Inc Seoul, Korea

Al Research Scientist

March 2022 - March 2024

- Developed a system for early diagnosis of lung cancer.
- Developing a tool for analyzing multiple diseases associated with dementia from brain MRI.

OSSTEM IMPLANT Seoul, Korea

Al Research Engineer March 2024 - Current

• Developing a Q&A AI system for answering questions from clients.

Skills_

Programming Python (Pandas, PyTorch, NumPy, Scikit-learn. etc.), C/C++

Miscellaneous Linux, Shell (Bash/Zsh), ETFX(Overleaf), Microsoft Office, Firebase, Git, Docker.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

Publications

JOURNAL ARTICLES

Effective pseudo-labeling based on heatmap for unsupervised domain adaptation in cell detection

Hyeonwoo Cho, Kazuya Nishimura, Kazuhide Watanabe, Ryoma Bise

Medical Image Analysis 79 (2022) p. 102436. Elsevier, 2022

CONFERENCE PROCEEDINGS

Cell detection in domain shift problem using pseudo-cell-position heatmap

Hyeonwoo Cho, Kazuya Nishimura, Kazuhide Watanabe, Ryoma Bise

Medical Image Computing and Computer Assisted Intervention–MICCAI 2021: 24th International Conference, Strasbourg, France, September 27–October 1, 2021, Proceedings, Part VIII 24, 2021

Semi-supervised cell detection in time-lapse images using temporal consistency

Kazuya Nishimura, Hyeonwoo Cho, Ryoma Bise

Medical Image Computing and Computer Assisted Intervention–MICCAI 2021: 24th International Conference, Strasbourg, France, September 27–October 1, 2021, Proceedings, Part VIII 24, 2021

Cell detection for various cell shapes

Cho Hyeonwoo, Kazuya Nishimura, Ryoma Bise

Record of 2020 Joint Conference of Electrical, Electronics and Information Engineers in Kyushu, 2020

April 8, 2024

UNDER REVIEW

- Recently submitted 2 papers to ECCV 2024! (Under Review)
- One paper is about test-time adaptation method for test-time distribution shift, the other one is about self-supervised method for universal segmentation.

Projects

Competition: Google - Isolated Sign Language Recognition

Seoul, Korea

VUNO February 2023 - May 2023

- · Achieved silver medal from this competition.
- Data: Time-Series, Tabular
- Main Approach: Self-Supervised Method (pretraining) Masked Auto Encoder
- More details: https://hyeonwoocho7.github.io/hwc.github.io/project/google-isolated-sign-language-recognition/

Lung Cancer DetectionSeoul, Korea

VUNO

March 2022 - October 2023

- Development of a solution for early detection and analysis of nodules that can develop into lung cancer from lung CT scan information of patients.
- Designed two stage detection algorithm for lung CT
- More details: https://hyeonwoocho7.github.io/hwc.github.io/project/lung-cancer-detection/

Domain Adaptation for Person Tracking

Fukuoka, Japan

Kyushu University

June 2021 - March 2022

- · Analyzed and handled multi object tracking datasets in various domains
- Defined a domain shift on a person tracking and developed domain adaptation methods using a center point based tracking method.
- Research Keyword: Domain Adaptation, Object Tracking, Pseudo labeling

Achievements

	2015	Korea-Japan Joint Scholarship Program, A full funding for undergraduate studies in science and	Korea
		engineering departments under the government of South Korea and the government of Japan	Noteu
	2021	N1, Japanese-Language Proficiency Test	Japan
	2021	850/999 , TOEIC	Japan
	2021	Level6, TOEIC Speaking	Japan
	2022	Excellent student award, Kyushu University graduation	Japan
	2023	Silver Medal, top5%, Kaggle: Google-Isolated Sign Language Recognition	Korea

Languages

English Professional Working Proficiency **Japanese** Full Professional Proficiency

April 8, 2024